[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们有与您期望看到的相同的语句集
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We have the same set of statements that you would expect to see
在C语言中，同样有一些不同之处。
in a C language, again with some differences.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们已经标记为Break，这很好。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We've got labeled break, which is good.
所以如果你有嵌套的循环和开关
So if you've got nested loops and switches and
东西，你可以打破内心深处的东西，这是好的。
stuff, you can break out of innermost things, which is good.
我们已经得到了for语句，我们可以使用它来迭代数组，但是
We've got the for statement which we can use to iterate through arrays but
我不建议使用那个。
I don't recommend using that.
在ES5中，我们获得了forEach方法，即map方法，您可以在其中
In ES5 we got the forEach method, the map method where you can
在数组的每个元素上调用一个函数。
have a function called on each element of the array.
这几乎消除了对for循环的所有需要，所以我不使用
That eliminates almost all need for the for loops, so I don't use for
再也不是圈圈了。
loops anymore.
我们有一个for in语句，它遍历所有
We have a for in statement which iterates through all of the names of all
对象的属性。
the properties of an object.
不幸的是，它还会迭代所有继承的属性
Unfortunately it also iterates through all of the inherited properties
这通常是你的方法，所以
which is usually your methods and so
你的方法和你的数据混在一起，就会变得一团糟。
your methods get mixed up with your data and it gets to be a mess.
幸运的是，在ES5中我们得到了Object.keys，它接受一个对象和
Fortunately we got, in ES5 we got Object.keys which takes an object and
返回一个字符串数组，它只是可枚举的
returns an array of strings which is just the enumerable
拥有对象的属性，这些属性通常是您想要的属性。
own properties of the object which are usually the ones you want.
因此，我不建议在任何一个中使用for。
So I don't recommend using for in either.
我们已经讨论了switch语句的问题。
We already talked about the problems with the switch statement.
但是关于switch语句有一件事。
One thing about the switch statement though.
JavaScript以一种方式改进了switch语句，并且
JavaScript improved the switch statement in one way and
也就是说，开关值不需要是数字。
that is that the switch value does not need to be a number.
它可以是一个非常漂亮的字符串，因为您可以打开更多的
It can be a string which can be very nice cuz you can switch on a greater set of
价值观。
values.
并且大小写的值可以是表达式，它们不必是常量。
And the case values can be expressions, they don't have to be constants.
因此这在进行国际化应用程序时非常有用，您可以
So that can be useful in doing internationalized applications that you
可以针对将返回该语言的yes值的函数进行大小写。
can case against a function which will return the yes value for this language.
这可能是件好事，&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：我们有例外
It could be a nice thing, &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: We have exception
用这种语言处理，这是很好的。
handling in this language which is nice.
在ES3之前我们没有，这意味着你必须编写程序
Before ES3 we didn't, which meant that you had to write programs
从来没有出过差错，因为没有办法从任何事情中恢复过来，
that never went wrong ever because there is no way to recover from anything,
这很难，所以我们现在有例外。
that was hard, so we got exceptions now.
你可以抛出字面上的任何值。
You can throw literally any value.
有一个惯例，你抛出的东西来自一个新的
There's a convention that you throw something that comes from a new
构造函数，与创建具有Name属性的对象相同，
constructor, which is the same as creating an object that has a name property,
和消息属性。
and a message property.
但实际上，你可以扔任何东西。
But in fact, you can throw literally anything.
因此，异常的使用方式与Java中有很大的不同。
So the way that exceptions are used is very different than in Java.
因此异常处理非常简单，因为我们没有异常类型。
And so exception handling is very simple because we don't have exception types.
只有一个捕获块，它捕获了所有内容。
There's only one catch block, and it catches everything.
一般来说，它会忽略它捕捉到的任何东西。
And generally, it's going to ignore whatever it caught.
它不在乎发生了什么。
It doesn't care what happened.
它所知道的是或者它所关心的只是没有起作用，所以
All it knows is or all it cares about is that didn't work, so
我们试试别的。
let's try something else.
也许它会起作用。
Maybe it'll work instead.
因此在Java中，您往往会看到用于实现某种形式计算机的异常，
So in Java you tend to see exceptions used to implement a form of computer go to,
在那里可以获得非常复杂的控制路径
where you can get very complicated control paths
由抛出异常的人指示的。
that are dictated by whoever threw the exception.
我认为这可能是一个很大的错误。
And I think that was probably a big mistake.
JavaScript没有犯那个特定的错误。
JavaScript didn't make that particular mistake.
所以我们倾向于正确地使用异常。
So we tend to use exceptions properly.
只在失败时使用它们。
Use them only for failures.
我们永远不会使用异常来执行正常的控制路径。
We'd never do normal control paths using exceptions.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：对不起。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Sorry.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；发言人2：你能澄清一下吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Could you clarify that?
我不明白那句话。
I didn't understand that statement.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：所以在Java中，人们倾向于研究为什么失败，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: So in Java there's a tendency to look at why did this fail,
好吧。
right.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不同的原因，不同的捕获，尝试异常A，异常B，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Different reasons, different catch, try exception A, exception B,
例外C
exception C.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：是的，没错。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah, exactly.
它有一个完整的例外情况，所以你知道谁抛出了例外，
It got a whole exception cases, and so you’ve got who threw the exception,
决定如何遍历代码和
deciding how you're gonna go through your code and
这通常意味着例外并不是真正的例外。
that usually means that the exceptions are not actually exceptional.
它们只是交替的控制路径，对吧？
They're just alternate control paths, right?
有时它是由你所拥有的类型系统中的弱点所驱动的
And sometimes it's motivated by weakness in the type system that you've got
希望返回int但
something that wants to return an int but
其他的事情也会发生，这并不是例外，只是不是int。
something else is gonna happen which is not exceptional, it's just not an int.
[声音]我用完了值，所以你会抛出异常。
[SOUND] I'm out of values and so you'll throw exception instead.
而在JavaScript中，因为我们是松散类型的，所以可以传递一个数字或
Whereas in JavaScript because we're loosely typed you can pass a number or
可以传递未定义的，也可以传递字符串，也可以传递对象，
you can pass undefined or you can pass a string, or you can pass an object,
你可以归还任何你需要的东西。
you can return anything that you need to.
所以这些都不是例外。
And so these things are not exceptions.
它们只是正常处理的更多模式。
They're just more modes of normal processing.
因此，您的控制流往往会变得更简单。
So your control flows tend to get much simpler.
还有其他问题吗？
Any other questions?
好了，这一小时到此结束。
Okay, so that's the end of this hour.
所以让我们休息一下，我们会回来的。
So let's take a break and we'll come back.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：嘿，我有一个来自聊天的快速问题。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Hey I have a quick question from chat.
人们问你为什么不使用for循环，而是喜欢每个循环。
People were asking why you don't use for loops and instead favor for each.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：是的。
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Yeah.
对每个人来说都是更好的选择。
For each is just much nicer.
一旦你习惯了它，它就更具可读性了。
Once you get used to it, it's more readable.
在该语言的未来版本中，它将是可瘫痪的。
In future versions of the language it's going to be paralyzable.
这是一个更现代的建筑。
It's a more modern construct.
它更实用。
It's more functional.
更容易作曲。
It's more composable.
这在各个方面都更好。
It's better in every aspect.
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：那你不能为每个人留下一个回执这一事实呢？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: What about the fact that you can't leave a for each with a return?
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：你说什么？
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I'm sorry?
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：事实是你不能为每个人留下a，就像stop a for
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: The fact that you can't leave a for each, like stop a for
每个循环。
each loop.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：你可以，你可以代替每次使用，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: You can, you can instead of using for each use every,
然后你可以让一些东西返回假，然后它就停止了。
and then you can have something return false and then it stops.